<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>CYBORG_ Brain</title>
      <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on CYBORG_ Brain</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Gods and AI</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Gods-and-AI</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Gods-and-AI</guid>
    <description>AI might be a reflection of our desire to create gods. Gods (typically/initially) tend to emerge in order to provide monitoring and access to strategic knowledge.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:53:48 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>What&#039;s with All the Dashes?</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/What's-with-All-the-Dashes</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/What's-with-All-the-Dashes</guid>
    <description>...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 17:31:14 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Virgule</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Virgule</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Virgule</guid>
    <description>(Hard ‘g’, rhymes with ‘mule’) The forward slash: / yes/no answer and/or ⇒ virgule example in text. Also used as the end of a line of poetry. he/him/his Poetry example from Robert Frost’s “The Road Not Taken”: “I took the one less traveled by, / And that has made all the difference.” Poetry/lyrics example from “My Immortal” by Evanescence: “I’m so tired of being here / Suppressed by all my childish fears” Script Want to see how many friends you still have after using esoteric typographic names for symbols? When you see a forward slash, call it a virgule! We use them all the time like showing our pronouns: he/him/his Or as an either/or option in our writing: and/or yes/no And also for writing poetry line breaks if you can’t format it line by line: “I’m so tired of being here / Suppressed by all my childish fears” So, what the hack is a virgule? It’s a fancy name for a forward slash.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 17:19:10 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Pathogenesis</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Pathogenesis</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Pathogenesis</guid>
    <description>Introduction Viruses …Viruses consist of genetic material, in the form of DNA, or its sister molecule, RNA, coated in protein. On their own they are an inert arrangement of matter, but when they manage to enter or infect the cell of a living thing, they take over its machinery and reproduce copies of themselves, bursting into life.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Spatial Dimension</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Spatial-Dimension</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Spatial-Dimension</guid>
    <description> Edward T. Hall, American anthropologist “We all have a spatial dimension, that determines our relationship to each other and our surroundings.” .</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 00:38:35 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Scientific Advertising</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Scientific-Advertising</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Scientific-Advertising</guid>
    <description>This book was published in 1923. Has clearly sexist themes, but otherwise reminds me that not much has changed in the last 100 years. Why? Possibly in part because evolution takes time—just because some of us get wise to psychology and tricks, doesn’t mean it stops working at scale.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 19:49:54 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Mechanical Intelligence</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Mechanical-Intelligence</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Mechanical-Intelligence</guid>
    <description>Using physical mechanics to perform some task (with or without human intervention). It’s about encapsulating your logic somehow through applied knowledge (a.k.a.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 19:35:56 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Digital Gardens</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Digital-Gardens</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Digital-Gardens</guid>
    <description>Idea that as we make connections and explore our notes, we “cultivate” new ideas or develop our ideas further. Notes act like a garden that grows over time.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 17:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Ship of Theseus</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Ship-of-Theseus</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Ship-of-Theseus</guid>
    <description>Thought experiment: if you have some thing and replace all of its parts one by one, do you still have the same thing? Called “Ship of Theseus,” because Plutarch posited that the Athenians ...</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 17:26:19 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Monsters</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Monsters</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Atoms/Monsters</guid>
    <description>Ancient Cyclops The Origin Story of this Terrifying One-Eyed Giant The Killer Origins of the Werewolf Modern Day Man or Bear? The Gift of Fear The harm of thinking the Book of Revelation ...</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 18:57:44 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>